let dummyData = {
  Philosophy: {
    title: 'Philosophy',
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'Who is considered the first greek philosopher?',
        answer: 'Tales of Mileto'
      },
      {
        question: 'Who is the main disciple of Socrates?',
        answer: 'Plato'
      },
      {
        question: 'Who is the most famous disciple of Plato?',
        answer: 'Aristotle'
      },
      {
        question: 'Who is the first great christian philosopher?',
        answer: 'Saint Augustine'
      },
      {
        question: 'Who wrote the "Summa contra gentiles"?',
        answer: 'Saint Thomas Aquinas'
      },
      {
        question: 'Who is considered the first modern philosopher?',
        answer: 'Ren√© Descartes'
      },
    ]
  },
  Literature: {
    title: 'Literature',
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'What are the two works of Homer?',
        answer: 'The Iliad and the Odyssey'
      },
      {
        question: 'What is the subject of the Iliad?',
        answer: 'The war of Troy'
      },
      {
        question: 'Who is the main character of the Odyssey?',
        answer: 'Odisseus or Ulysses'
      },
      {
        question: 'Who wrote the AEneid?',
        answer: 'Virgil'
      },
    ]
  },
  React: {
    title: 'React',
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'What is React?',
        answer: 'A library for managing user interfaces'
      },
      {
        question: 'Where do you make Ajax requests in React?',
        answer: 'The componentDidMount lifecycle event'
      }
    ]
  },
  JavaScript: {
    title: 'JavaScript',
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'What is a closure?',
        answer: 'The combination of a function and the lexical environment within which that function was declared.'
      }
    ]
  },
}

export default dummyData
